Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Previously on
Star Trek: Strange New Worlds...
My sacrifice will save the livs
of those I care most about.
- It's time for me to go.
- I've let something out.
- It's your emotions.
- I can't control it.
Mr. Kirk. clean your mess.
T'Pring and I have decided
to take time apart.
I am conflicted
because I have feelings
for someone else.
I don't want to suppress
this one any longer.
Those events were never
supposed to happen
and you were never meant
to be aware of them.
I have to insist
that you not share
any of what you experienced
from this time.
Buy me a drink next time
we're on starbase together.
That. uh. sounds lovely.
The people you love the most
can cause you the most pain.
but it's the people you love
that can mend your heart
when you feel broken.
Communications Officer's Log.
stardate 2394.8.
Enterprise has been sent
to Bannon's Nebula.
on the edge of explored space.
I've seen a lot of nebulas.
but this one's special.
It's a stellar nursery.
the birthplace of new stars.
But that's not why we're here.
The nursery is also full
of deuterium... starship fuel.
Starfleet's building an outpost
here to collect and refine it.
if they can ever get it workin.
Amazing to think that
a million years from now.
those brand-new stars
will shine down
on explorers just like us.
but this place will look
entirely different by then.
Uhura.
You awake there. Ensign?
My eyes are
technically open. Captain.
Just didn't get much sleep
last night.
Or the last ten.
Oh. Well. I appreciate
all the work you've put into
coordinating this mission.
but you generally only want
to burn the candle at one end.
I'll take that under advisement.
The crew of the refinery
sends their greetings
and they're waiting
for our engineering details.
Have Chief Kyle stand by
to initiate transport.
I hear congratulations
are in order. Fleet Captain.
- Stop it.
- Fleet Captain?
I've been given command of
the refinery and the Farragut.
just until we get
the station on line.
Well. it's the shiniest
gas station I've ever seen.
Well. it's not just
a gas station. Lieutenant.
It's right at the edge
of the frontier.
It unlocks half the quadrant.
It'll be the jumping-off point
for the next great age
of exploration.
Oh. good. I was afraid
I'd miss the speech.
Well. I started earlier
but Uhura fell asleep.
I assumed Starfleet's
primary motivation
was the nebula's proximity
to Gorn space.
Sadly. you're probably right.
Their presence is growing.
This will help us counter it.
Which is why the refinery
needs to be finished
- as soon as possible.
- While the refinery
is off-line.
Enterprise'scollectors
are operational.
though the process
may be slower.
It would be logical to use this
opportunity to refuel ourselves.
My thoughts exactly. Mr. Spock.
Ortegas. find us a dense pocket
of deuterium and do some laps.
Rip some doughnuts through
the gas cloud. aye. sir.
Nice and slow. we don't want to
use more fuel than we collect.
Activating Bussard collectors.
Refueling underway. Captain.
Sorry to interrupt. Captain.
I'm receiving a signal.
On speakers.
Any time. Ensign.
Uh...
- It's gone.
- Can you play back
the recording?
I can't find it. sir.
It was there. Captain.
- It's probably just a glitch...
- I'll run a full diagnostic
on the communication system.
First. disable
the subspace antenna.
Check for a charge
on the EPS manifold
before disconnecting this tap.
Perfect.
Now. if there's
any residual ionization.
- here is where you'll find it.
- Uh.
what the hell
- are you doing
inside my nacelle?
- Sorry.
I am recalibrating
the communications array.
The antenna assembly
goes through the nacelles.
I like to be thorough.
and I've asked for so many
of these recalibrations that
eventually Hemmer got annoyed
and said it would be easier
to show me how to do it myself.
You know.
"teach a cadet to fish."
So we made a recording.
Hemmer was our chief engineer.
before he...
I know.
He was one of my best students.
I'm sorry. I just said that
because he's dead.
Actually. he was just okay.
But look...
Look what he made of himself.
Right.
Anyway. I'm almost done.
How come you never
talked to me before?
Uh. I'm... I'm sure I have.
Oh. no.
- No. no.
- Oh.
I'm sorry.
I've just been busy. I guess.
Welcome to the Enterprise.
here is where you'll find i.
Now. what do you do next?
I don't know.
I won't let you
blow up the ship. I promise.
Not that!
- Important lesson:
be less gullible.
- Hey!
Back to work.
Let's start by turning down the
gain on the subspace antenna...
Between us and the bulkhead.
the whole project's
been a fiasco.
The refinery was supposed
to be on line two months ago.
What's slowing it down?
"Organizational difficulties"
was the polite term
that Starfleet used.
Their previous superintendent
got shipped back to Earth.
which is why they could
really use your version of...
managerial fervor?
Mm! Nothing beats cleaning up
somebody else's mess.
Space.
The final frontier.
These are the voyages
of the starshipEnterprise.
Its five-year mission:
to explore strange new worlds..
To seek out new life
and new civilizations.
to boldly go
where no one has gone before.
Based on what you heard and saw.
and the elevated readings
from your visual cortex.
I'd say it's pretty clear
you were hallucinating.
You said you had just watched
a video of Hemmer.
His death was fresh
in your mind.
Starfleet officers
aren't supposed to
randomly hallucinate.
You didn't do anything wrong.
And there was nothing
random about it.
While working in the nacelle
you were exposed
to a small amount
of refined deuterium.
which can be dangerous.
You have a mild case
of deuterium poisoning.
And that can cause
terrifying hallucinations?
It can.
You could also
experience headaches.
blurred vision. nausea.
This should help
with the symptoms.
But there is
something else here.
Your serotonin
and cortisol levels.
You haven't been sleeping.
Oh.
It's been a busy...
year.
Exhaustion can exacerbate
the effects
of deuterium poisoning.
You need to rest.
How am I supposed to sleep
after what I just saw?
I empathize.
But I also know a stubborn
patient when I see one.
You aren't going back on duty
until I'm satisfied
you've slept.
Head to Deck Seven.
get to work stabilizing
the life-support grid.
Aye. sir.
It's not as bad as it looks.
It's way worse.
The central refining
and storage systems
all seem to be in good shape.
Have you looked
at the maintenance logs?
Because you get the feeling
that this place has been
breaking down a lot faster
than the crew is able to fix it.
Luckily. we have
three crews now.
Enterpriseand Farragut'steams
can mop up the problem systems
while the station's teams
get the refinery running.
Yes.
But if there is
an underlying issue.
and it smells like there is.
we ought to figure that out.
I typically don't base
my decision-making
off of feelings and smells.
Oh.
Any underlying issues
will become clear as we work.
Mm.
Aye aye. Commander.
Hello?
- Sam.
- Jimmy.
Welcome to the Enterprise.
Hell of a ship.
And they let you work here?
What can I say?
Captain Pike
asked for the more handsome
Kirk brother.
You want a tour?
As long as it ends at the bar.
So. what's new and exciting
in the world
of xenoanthropology?
Literally everything
in xenoanthropology
is new and exciting.
But instead of giving you
a long answer
you don't actually care about.
why don't we skip to your news?
Wow.
Sensing some
hostility there. Sam.
Not at all.
Congrats. Jim.
First officer of the Farragut.
Well. not for
another few months.
I still have to train
my replacement.
Still. it's quite
an achievement.
Thank you.
And youngest first officer
in the whole fleet.
Youngest first officer ever.
actually.
I don't suppose you remember
who held the record before you?
Ah. okay.
That's what this is.
It was George Kirk. Sr.
First officer of the Kelvin.
Dad gave you his first name.
even if you choose
not to use it.
so I have to do something
to keep up.
You're making me look...
Like what?
Sam. what does my ambition
have to do with you?
Dad has a very
old-fashioned idea
of what a successful career
looks like.
what a fulfilling life
and it just so happens
it looks a lot like you.
Well. if you're so worried
about impressing Dad.
then why are you wallowing
in a science lab?
Wallowing. seriously?
Records are made to be broken.
I put in some legwork
to beat this one. So what?
We can make the old man proud
in our own ways.
Or not at all.
Finally! Okay.
life support's been stabilized.
Are you kidding me?
We need to send a team
to Deck Five
to get the EPS regulators
back on line.
Yes. Well. that is going
to have to wait.
One of my teams found something
in the fuel distribution system.
That system was on line already.
What were you...
You disobeyed my direct orders
and went digging around
in the functioning systems...
If I had followed your orders
to the letter.
we would never have found
evidence of sabotage.
Sabotage?
Your move.
I know.
Is that not a polite euphemism
for "make your move faster"?
Am I boring you. Mr. Spock?
Decidedly not.
Your move.
There is a matter
I've been meaning to discuss.
Should I get a drink first?
You sound serious.
Starfleet is built
on a command hierarchy.
Fraternization can lead to...
complications.
- As such. there are protocols...
- You want to tell Starfleet
about us.
If there is anything to tell.
Your move.
Relationships...
at least for humans. can be...
quantum things.
Think about Schroödinger's cat...
They exist or
they don't.
- depending on
who's observing them.
- That is...
Not how quantum superposition
actually works?
Yeah. I know.
It's a-a metaphor. Spock.
A messy one.
Just like
whatever this is.
My point is
if we let Starfleet...
Or anyone else.
for that matter...
Look inside the box. then...
Our quantum cat
might disappear.
I'd just as soon let it live.
see how big it grows.
- Your move.
- Excuse me.
- Ensign. aren't you...
- Supposed to be resting. sir.
yes. but...
Everybody ignores the "orders"
part of doctor's orders.
I don't have
deuterium poisoning.
When I saw Hemmer
on the turbolift.
I heard the same sound
that I heard on the bridge.
but I heard it on the bridge
before I went into the nacelle.
before I was exposed
to deuterium.
You believe your hallucinations
began on the bridge.
Logic would suggest that
the simplest solution is often
the correct one. right?
You seem to be the only
Enterprisecrewmember affected.
Scans show nothing in the sector
that would explain
your symptoms.
Logic would suggest
exposure to a known hallucinogen
is a more likely source
of hallucinations than...
Than nothing at all.
Yeah. I looked at your chart.
Nyota.
It's... You have a textbook case
of overwork and exhaustion.
I can prescribe you something
to help you sleep.
Sleeping is the last thing
I want to do right now.
Saurian brandy.
Coming right up.
Your. uh. Vulcan buddy
should protect his queen.
He was two moves away
from checkmate
until you distracted him.
now he's in trouble.
James Kirk.
Uhura.
You're Sam's brother.
Oh.
You're friends with Sam.
Look.
I really don't want
to be hit on right now.
Oh.
You're friends with Sam.
Come on.
Nobody's hitting on anyone.
You sat next to me.
You just look like
you could use a friend.
I appreciate the sentiment.
but I am not in the market
for friends right now.
It's not real.
I told you
I am not hitting on you.
I am so sorry.
- I can't believe I...
- Yeah. I can't believe it.
either.
You seem so pleasant.
I will walk you to sickbay.
Dr. M'Benga will fix you up.
Whoa. hold on. You really
want to take me to sickbay
and explain all this?
I mean. it looked to me
like you were seeing something
that wasn't there.
You have big enough problems
to worry about
without being written up
for striking a superior officer.
I have a dermal regenerator
in my quarters.
- Come on.
- Ow. ow.
- You're making it worse.
- You're being a baby.
- Ah...
- I'm done.
I think your nightmare visions
are turning you into a sadist.
You think it's all in my head.
Of course not.
Look. I-I've had
deuterium poisoning.
and I've gone days
without sleep.
but I have never
punched an officer
because of either one.
The point is
I'm an exquisite
judge of character.
and I believe you.
There's something else
going on here.
And if you'll let me.
I can help you figure out what.
Okay. I've triple-checked
the sensor logs.
and there's nothing
but deuterium out there.
But something must be
doing this to me.
No one else has reported
the same symptoms?
M'Benga says I'm the only one.
On the Enterprise. anyway.
Good idea.
I'll check in
with the Farragut'sdoctor.
Can I bring her
your medical record?
You gonna be okay alone?
Yeah. Just. uh...
don't punch any more officers
until I get back.
Well. this would be a lot easier
if you'd gotten the station's
lighting grid on line.
Or the internal sensors.
Yes. but if I had done that.
we might have just exploded
and never known why.
It's too close.
It's too close. it's too close.
it can't breathe.
Our saboteur is Starfleet?
What is he saying?
Get away from me.
Get him away from me.
Get him away!
There's nothing there.
Nobody's gonna hurt you.
This isn't real.
It can't be real.
Are you real?
What's your name?
Ramon.
Saul Ramon.
Lieutenant Ramon. why
did you sabotage the station?
Sabotage?
That... that isn't real.
It's-it's not real.
Enterprise. we have
a medical emergency.
What's going on. Captain?
Contact Starfleet. We're
being attacked by an enemy...
Ensign Uhura.
You're supposed to be
on medical leave. are you not?
As your captain. I need
all my officers healthy.
both physically and mentally.
As your friend.
I just want to help you
understand what's happening.
You know.
the irony's not lost on me.
The communications officer
who can't communicate
what's wrong with her.
Come in.
Lieutenant Kirk.
That's right.
It's an honor to meet you. sir.
Congratulations on
your promotion to Fleet Captain.
Uh. it's temporary.
I came to find Ensign Uhura.
I ran into her earlier
and I was concerned.
- As am I.
Not the time. got it.
I heard one of the station's
crew was arrested for sabotage.
That's right. I had him beamed
to sickbay for evaluation.
Farragut'smedical officer
got a call about him yesterday.
One of his friends
was worried about him.
said he kept talking about
seeing things
that weren't there.
Ring a bell?
We need to know
what you saw. Lieutenant.
It's the only way
we can help you.
He might not understand us.
There's significant damage
to the speech and language
centers of his brain.
And it's getting worse.
His auditory nerves
are firing wildly.
I'm fine.
Go after him.
Security to Deck Four!
This isn't real.
Nyota. wake up. this isn't real.
- No. hey. Uhura.
- This isn't...
This is very real. okay?
You aren't imagining it.
Okay.
We have to stop Ramon
before he hurts anyone else.
Come on.
Emergency lighting activated.
Sickbay. we need
immediate medical assistance
outside Astrometrics.
Acknowledged. sending a medic.
Captain.
Ramon cut the power conduits.
That's why it went dark.
Definitely gonna make
finding him harder.
Stay with her.
Ramon's headed
towards Engineering.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Okay. maybe not.
James?
Hey.
I got you.
What happened?
Sorry. I can't. I should
just go back to sickbay.
-I'll walk back with you.
Come on.
-No.
You keep searching for Ramon.
I'll be fine.
I promise.
James?
You two know each other?
Now's not the time
to explain. Captain.
If you haven't
seen Ramon. then...
He must have found
a hole to hide in.
We should double back.
Uhura to all teams.
I may have found
Lieutenant Ramon
in the access tunnel
to the port nacelle.
I'm not far. Wait for me.
Step away from the console.
Listen. the things
you've been seeing...
I've been seeing them. too.
I understand.
But whatever it is you saw
that made you come here.
it wasn't real.
None of it.
But I am.
My name is Nyota.
I'm the communications officer.
I-I was born in Kenya.
I used to have a cat
named Kamili.
My-my first memory
is watching my dad
play the piano.
I'm real.
Ramon. please.
I am begging you.
Step away from the console.
I don't want to blow
either of us up. Please!
Fuel pod ejection
sequence initiated.
-Emergency transport.
Beam us out. now.
-Wait!
Two dead. chief medical officer
in surgery.
the ship almost disabled.
and we have no idea why.
When Ramon was in sickbay.
he seemed to be hearing
the same sound
I've been hearing.
The way I see it.
that's good news.
You're not crazy.
Something is affecting you.
the same way it affected him.
And we're gonna figure out what.
I think you should confine me
to my quarters. Captain.
Why?
How long until
I'm sabotaging the ship
- or jumping out of an airlock?
- Oh.
It won't come to that.
I promise you.
Now I need to talk
to Commander Chin-Riley
and find out how much damage
Ramon did to the refinery.
Getting it on line is critical.
But since
Lieutenant Ramon is deceased.
Starfleet gave me permission
to decrypt his personal logs
and private medical files.
Maybe there's answers in there.
James Kirk.
Sam's brother.
La'An Noonien-Singh.
Stickler for
orderly security records.
Were-were you injured?
Uh. no. I am just. uh.
waiting for Ensign Uhura.
Oh. Right.
- I didn't know you were friends.
- Oh. we just met.
I happened to be there
when she needed some help.
Although she seems like
the type who has trouble
asking anyone for help.
especially her friends.
And you're the type who can't
walk past a stranger in need.
What?
My. uh. my dad was in Starfleet.
My mom. my brother and I.
we spent my whole childhood
chasing him
from one posting to another.
barely seeing him.
When I'd ask why.
my mom would always say.
"He's helping people
who really need it."
But when you're a kid.
you think...
Why does he care more about
strangers than he does about me?
So you tell yourself.
"Hey. if my dad chose
helping total strangers over me.
it must... must be important."
As one of those strangers
that Starfleet helped.
I promise you...
it is.
I. uh. I should
finish my rounds.
Good evening. Lieutenant.
I haven't forgotten that drink
you owe me. by the way.
Looks like the routing system
is almost back on line.
You should be on Enterprise.
supervising the repairs there.
That's what I told him.
but Captain Pike disagrees.
Getting the station on line
remains the first priority.
I got to know... what exactly
is your problem with me?
I don't have a problem with you.
I have a problem
with the situation.
That is malarkey.
and you know it.
You're sloppy.
Okay?
You don't respect protocols.
You're too loose
with discipline.
You don't follow orders
unless you feel like it.
and you have crumbs
on your uniform.
When did you even eat?
You're like...
a space hippie.
Ooh.
Well. I have been
called more names
than there are stars in the sky.
but "space hippie"
is a new one on me.
I think you've gotten
too used to being
the smartest person in the room.
I don't think I'm
Oh. sure you do.
You hide behind
order and discipline
because it kills you
when someone has the nerve
to question your decisions.
You don't think
my years of experience
should buy me any deference?
You've been in Starfleet
since before I was born.
but I outrank you.
Why do you think that is?
I'll have the station on line
in a few hours.
I swear I saw John
standing in the mess hall.
like he never...
Like he was still alive.
And I tried
to say something to him.
and everyone just stared at me.
They thought I'd lost my mind.
And that noise...
I think I am losing my mind.
He was having the same kind
of hallucinations as me.
Hearing the same sound.
His...
his brain scans show activity
in the same region.
But his case was more severe.
Or it just started earlier.
I mean. based on the date
of these logs.
I may be...
a day and a half
from losing my mind entirely.
Look. why don't we just
take a break. all right?
Update Captain Pike
on our progress.
or lack thereof.
Maybe get something to eat.
I hear the mess
is serving real cookies.
not from the matter synthesizer.
I don't need a cookie.
Okay. now you sound crazy.
I'm sorry. it was a dumb joke.
It's not a joke.
That's the problem.
This isn't the first time
I've seen something like this.
Imagined someone
who isn't there.
A few years ago.
I lost my parents and my brother
in a shuttle accident.
I-I wasn't there
when it happened.
I never saw
the crash site. but...
after they died.
it felt like every time
I closed my eyes.
I'd see it.
The crash. their final moments.
I don't know
what to say. except...
I'm sorry.
Got so bad I couldn't even
look at pictures of them.
Just seeing their faces...
And then Hemmer died.
and it all came back.
But I kept covering it with work
and smiles and more work.
The truth is I've never
been able to face death.
Everyone has some way
of dealing with it
and moving on. but I just...
I don't know how.
How can I be a Starfleet officer
if I can't handle death?
Maybe you can't.
Look. I could tell you
some comforting fairy tale.
but we both know the truth.
Our job puts us up against death
more than is fair.
And we might not like it.
but we do have to face it.
And right now. death is winning.
It claimed your family.
it claimed your friend.
It convinced you to forget them.
because it's less painful than
holding on to their memories.
Now. you can let death win...
or you can fight back.
Hold on to them.
Still no to that cookie?
Be right back.
Not that!
Important lesson:
be less gullible.
Hey!
Let's start with
dialing down the gain
on the subspace antenna.
or else you'll
burn out the receiver.
Burn out the receiver.
Got the last one.
Thought we could split it.
Forget about the stupid cookie
for a second.
I think I figured something out.
Ramon's brain scan.
What am I supposed
to be noticing?
There was damage to the language
center of his brain.
My brain scan shows elevated
activity in the same spot.
And we were both hearing
that same sound.
What if someone or something
was trying to communicate
with him.
with me.
but their signal's too strong?
So strong it that burned out
that area of his brain entirely.
It's a message from some...
invisible alien?
You want to talk to Sam.
don't you?
Your symptoms started
once we arrived
in the nebula. right?
So it makes sense that our
mystery alien would live here.
But our sensors aren't
showing any life-forms.
Well. there's a theory...
It's a little bit fringe.
but hear me out...
That extra-dimensional
life-forms
could actually
poke into our space
and attach themselves
to atoms from our dimension.
Meaning they aren't
sophisticated life-forms
capable of speech
or even language.
There are similarities
in the ways different species
process thoughts. ideas.
That's how the universal
translator works...
By recognizing
those similarities.
Maybe my brain
is doing the same thing?
Invisible aliens
are using your brain
as a universal translator.
It might be the only way
they know how to communicate.
They send simple ideas to
the language center of my brain.
then my brain interprets
those ideas the only way
it can...
Through my thoughts.
my memories.
The visions.
they're like vocabulary.
What are they trying to say?
I felt the walls closing in
because they feel
trapped.
I was attacking myself because
we're responsible.
They showed me
the ship exploding
because they are desperate
to break free. but...
We're killing them.
We're killing
the ones they love.
and they're terrified.
And that's what
they're making me feel.
If they're living in the nebula.
in the deuterium...
In a way.
they are the deuterium.
So. then when
we pull the deuterium
out of the nebula
into our nacelles.
and when the station
processes and refines it...
We're basically torturing them.
Uhura to Captain Pike.
Sir. we need to stop the fuel
refinery from being activated.
I'm not sure what's going on.
Ensign. but it's too late.
The refinery was activated
five minutes ago.
Captain. you have to
shut down the station!
It's a matter of life or death!
I'll contact Una
and do what I can.
Nothing's working.
The refinery's automated systems
aren't responding
to any commands.
It's not shutting down.
Perhaps Lieutenant Ramon
did more damage than we thought.
Bridge.
Keep going.
You all right?
The station's emergency shutdown
procedures aren't working.
You mind telling me
why we need to
shut it down in the first place?
We believe there's
some sort of alien life-form...
We're killing them. Captain.
The creatures that live
in the deuterium in the nebula...
We're killing them
by pulling them into
our fuel pods and our nacelles.
and now the station's
doing the same thing.
but at a much larger scale.
But we can't see them
or detect them in any way.
I can hear them.
So could Ramon.
They're screaming for our help.
Ramon died trying to save them.
Captain. you told me
the point of this station
was to help us find
new forms of life.
But what is the point
of exploring
if we're just gonna
kill what we find?
We can't shut it down.
Then we need to destroy it.
How certain are you?
I'm certain. Captain.
What's the play?
Hail the refinery.
order an emergency evacuation.
then vent all the deuterium
from Enterprise'sfuel pods.
Order the Farragut
to do the same.
You heard her.
Aye. sir.
Attention. All refinery crew
and maintenance teams.
evacuate immediately.
Repeat: all...
No life signs aboard.
All crew have safely
cleared the refinery.
Fire torpedoes!
Torpedoes away.
Did that work?
Uhura. what is it?
We did it.
They're safe.
That's it?
Yeah.
That's it.
The jumping-off point
for a new era of exploration.
Well...
Starfleet can build a
new gas station someplace else.
One where there isn't anything
living in the deuterium.
And if there's any blowback.
it's on me.
End of the day.
that was my call. Okay?
Or we can tell 'em
someone's brash influence
rubbed off on you.
Always happy to be of service.
You know. I was thinking.
you discovered
a completely new form of life.
They might give you a medal.
And now. if you don't mind.
would you take your station.
Hail the Farragut.
As soon as we've collected
all of our escape pods.
let's get out of this nebula
before we cause any more damage.
And then I am going
to need Admiral Nagawa
on my private channel.
And after that.
go take a nap.
That's an order.
Starship Maintenance 307.
Starship Maintenance.
what about it?
You were my professor
at the Academy.
Oh. I remember.
You gave me a C.
And you deserved that C.
My final paper was
meticulously researched.
It was sloppy.
But for what it's worth.
that well-deserved C
is absolutely not
what's been bothering you.
It's Hemmer.
I'm a reminder that your friend
died and I replaced him.
And every time you see me.
it dredges up
all of that sadness.
I get it.
I've been there.
Too many times.
And if you want to keep saying
it's the C.
I don't have to contradict you.
It's your family?
My mother always knew
how to make me laugh.
It's been a long time
since I've been able
to look at that.
To staying in the fight.
Why do you think they chose me?
You were exactly
what they needed.
Thoughtful. empathetic.
You heard them.
I mean. maybe all it took
was a good listener.
Well. I'm glad to see
that everything
worked out for the best.
And I think
I'm gonna write a paper
about our deuterium friends.
- Hey.
- Oh. Wow. Sounds thrilling.
I've been wanting to say...
the Farragut
is lucky to have you. Jim.
I'm proud of you.
Honestly.
Thanks. Sam.
What is happening right now?
I'm not sure. either.
You're seriously
not gonna apologize?
For what... for being
extremely competent?
For being a...
Okay.
You know what?
Forget it.
Go have fun
on your stupid little ship.
I'm gonna be here.
on the flagship.
Well.
- that was something.
- Yeah. it's just
Sam being Sam.
- Sometimes he can be. uh...
- Frustrating.
James. meet our
chief science officer.
Mr. Spock.
Spock. meet James Kirk.
first officer of the Farragut.
Why don't you join us?
Yeah.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org